Class of 1983 Records 1979-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1983 Records
1979-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1983.
RG 80 UUID:24bbc166-441d-4c0c-9769-4124c6363c19
6 boxes (2.9 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1983.
The Class of 1983 was the 105th graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1983 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1983, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1983 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1983 (Box 2283, Folder 1)
- Commencement Speaker 1983 (Box 2283, Folder 2)
- Freshman Handbook 1979-1980 (Box 2283, Folder 3)
- Ivy Day 1983 (Box 2283, Folder 4)
- Last Chapel 1983 (Box 2283, Folder 5)
- Class Letters 1983-2003 (Box 2283, Folder 6)
- New Faces 1979-1980 (Box 2283, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1988 (Box 2283, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1993 (Box 2283, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1998 (Box 2283, Folder 10)
- Reunions 2003 (Box 2283, Folder 11)
- Sophomore Year Scrapbook Contents 1980-1981 (Box 2285)
- Yearbook Photographs (Box 2286)
  - A 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 1)
  - B-Bl 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 2)
  - Bi-Bo 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 3)
  - Bo-Bz 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 4)
  - C-Ci 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 5)
  - Cl-Coh 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 6)
  - Coll-Cu 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 7)
  - D 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 8)
  - E 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 9)
  - F-Fi 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 10)
  - Fo-Fu 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 11)
  - Ga-Gi 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 12)
  - Go-Gu 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 13)
  - Ha 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 14)
  - He-Hu 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 15)
  - I-J 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 16)
  - Ka-Ke 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 17)
  - Kh-Ky 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 18)
  - L 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 19)
  - Ma-Me 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 20)
  - Mi-Mu 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 21)
  - N 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 22)
  - O 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 23)
  - Pa-Pe 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 24)
  - Pi-Pu 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 25)
  - R 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 26)
  - Sa-Se 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 27)
  - Sq-Sm 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 28)
  - Sn-Sw 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 29)
  - Ta-To 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 1)
  - Tr-Tu 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 2)
  - U-V 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 3)
  - W-Wh 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 4)
  - Wi-Wr 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 5)
  - Y 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 6)
  - Z 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 7)
- Academic Scenes 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 8)
- Athletics 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 9)
- Davis Center Scenes 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 10)
- Editing Materials 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 11)
- Events-Outdoor 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 12)
- Faculty Groups 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 13)
- House Activities 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 14)
- House Groups A-D 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 15)
- House Groups E-H 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 16)
- House Groups I-O 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 17)
- House Groups P-Z 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 18)
- Outdoor Scenes 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 20)
- Sports 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 21)
- Not Used 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 22)
- Students Outdoors 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 23)
- Student Clubs 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 24)